<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on PH-Tools.CarbonCheck</title>
    <link>https://ph-tools.github.io/CarbonCheck/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on PH-Tools.CarbonCheck</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://ph-tools.github.io/CarbonCheck/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Install</title>
      <link>https://ph-tools.github.io/CarbonCheck/install/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ph-tools.github.io/CarbonCheck/install/</guid>
      <description>Comparing the performance of your proposed building design to a standard &amp;lsquo;baseline&amp;rsquo; is a common practice among many energy-modeling workflows. This is especially true for any project seeking public funding to offset the costs of high-performance building components. However, constructing this &amp;lsquo;baseline&amp;rsquo; model can be a time-consuming and error-prone task for modeling teams. This is where CarbonCheck comes in: a new tool specifically designed for New York State Passive House projects, designed to streamline the process of creating baseline models.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baselines</title>
      <link>https://ph-tools.github.io/CarbonCheck/baselines/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ph-tools.github.io/CarbonCheck/baselines/</guid>
      <description>Creating Baseline Models CarbonCheck includes tools to create automatic baseline versions of your PHPP or WUFI-Passive energy models. These features allow you to specify a &amp;lsquo;source&amp;rsquo; model which describes your proposed design, and then CarbonCheck will modify this model to match the requirements of the New York State Energy Conservation Code baseline configuration. The exact baseline specifications used will vary depending on the climate zone and other building attributes. For more information on the baseline settings required, see the NYS Energy Code | Section C407.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reporting</title>
      <link>https://ph-tools.github.io/CarbonCheck/reporting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ph-tools.github.io/CarbonCheck/reporting/</guid>
      <description>Creating Output Reports CarbonCheck includes tools for creating automatic output reports with the data from both a &amp;lsquo;baseline&amp;rsquo; design and your proposed design side by side for easy comparison. For more details on creating baseline models, see the Baselines page.
Step 1. Load Project Data The first step is to open the CarbonCheck Application and read in the basic project data from your Passive House model. This will read in things like the project address, client information, and other basic data about the site and climate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>https://ph-tools.github.io/CarbonCheck/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ph-tools.github.io/CarbonCheck/faq/</guid>
      <description>FAQ: Is CarbonCheck really free? Yes! CarbonCheck is free to download and use. You can find all the source code at the GitHub repository. It was developed by bldgtyp and the Passive House Accelerator team to help the New York State Passive House community. This project is made possible by the support of the New York State Energy Research and Development Authority (NYSERDA).
Can CarbonCheck baseline models be used for New York State Energy Code compliance?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://ph-tools.github.io/CarbonCheck/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ph-tools.github.io/CarbonCheck/contact/</guid>
      <description>PH-Tools? PH-Tools is the umbrella project encompassing all of the various software tools we&amp;rsquo;ve been building to make Passive House energy modeling faster, easier and more fun. In the past we&amp;rsquo;ve made plugins for DesignPH, and tool-kits like Honeybee-PH for Rhino and Honeybee modeling. We are happy to include CarbonCheck in the roster, with the goal of helping New York State Passive House teams automatically generate baseline variants and easily output building data.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
